Street & Smith Records
Street & Smith Records
- Editorial files, by title
  - Miscellaneous manuscripts
    - The Man Who Saw the Sea on Fire / Carroll E. Robb (Box 269)
    - A Man's Making / S.S. Gordon [S.G. Shaw], includes editorial note (Box 269)
    - Many Are the Ways / R.V. Young (Box 269)
    - A Marriage of Honor / John Chancellor, 3 folders (Box 269)
    - Melting Point / R.V. Young (Box 269)
    - The Men With the Scars / Howard Fitzalan, paste-up from the pages of The Popular Magazine (Box 269)
    - The Militant Meekling [alternate title: "Yaller"] / Lester Lear, includes another version (Box 269)
    - Mimi Pinson / Alfred de Musset, includes Contes, VI in series Oeuvres Completes de Alfred de Musset, nouv. ed., from which selection has been translated (Box 269)
    - Miscast [alternate title: "The Wrong Role"] / Henry Leverage (Box 269)
    - Mr. Davy Jones Jr. / Edmund Elliot [a.k.a. Elliot Balestier] (Box 269)
    - The Moving Points / R.V. Young (Box 269)
    - Murder By Mail a Pinklin West Story / Thorne Miller [a.k.a. Chris B. Booth?], partial manuscript (Box 269)
    - Museum Piece / Beverley Owen (Box 269)
    - Muskeeters [sic] of the Marne / A.B. Ility [a.k.a. H. Bedford-Jones] (Box 269)
    - The Narrative of 'Z. Roe Cypher, Esq.' [alternate title: "The Good in the Worst of Us"] / George Bronson-Stoward, includes editorial notes (Box 269)
    - Navy Cross / Dale DeV. Kier (Box 270)
    - New Wine Skins / J. Irby Koon (Box 270)
    - Next Move? / John Fellows, includes editorial note (Box 270)
    - No Pawn for Glamour / Edward J. McKinney (Box 270)
    - On Asgard's Brink / Olaf Aarrestad [a.k.a. O.N. Massey], includes editorial note (Box 270)
    - On Society and the American Navy / Frank S. Arnett, including an Interview with Rear Admiral Joseph B. Coghlan (Box 270)
    - On Society in the American Army / Frank S. Arnett, including an Interview with Major General Frederick D. Grant (Box 270)
    - On Society in the Land of the Sultan / Frank S. Arnett, including an Interview with Hon. Oscar S. Straus (Box 270)
    - On Strollers and Society / Frank S. Arnett, including an Interview with the Late Sir Henry Irving (Box 270)
    - On the Dog / Olaf Aarrestad [a.k.a. O.N. Massey] (Box 270)
    - One Ear and the Man / Frank J. Leahy (Box 270)
    - One Leg in Limbo / Clint Osborne and Elizabeth Evans (Box 270)
    - One Man's Valley / Van Cort, includes rejection (Box 270)
    - One Must Be Chosen / Hal Annas (Box 270)
    - The Open Door / Dorothy Bennett (Box 270)
    - The Orchid of Romance [alternate title: "The Orchid of Creeping Terror"] / Donald Bayne Hobart, includes editorial note (Box 270)
    - The Other Way / Clifford Dowdey (Box 270)
    - Our Fingerprint Department / Benjamin Call (Box 270)
    - The Oxidization of Inspector Swinny / Frank Blighton (Box 270)
    - Perilous Street / Jesse F. Gelders (Box 270)
    - Piano Jim / Bertrand W. Sinclair, paste-up from the pages of The Popular Magazine (Box 270)
    - The Pin of Death, Chapter 1: A Legacy of Mystery / Christopher B. Booth, partial manuscript (Box 270)
    - Po'h Boy / Mary Stoddard MacFee (Box 270)
    - Port o' London [alternate title: Ships from Seven Seas"] / M.L. Eliott [Marie Louise Eliott] (Box 270)
    - Port of Call / J.M. Hoffman (Box 270)
    - Practical Detective Talks / Cyrus Chapin (Box 270)
    - The Prey / R.V. Young (Box 270)
    - The Price of Success / Bertrand Royal (Box 270)
    - The Quests of Matthew Quaintance / Mattock Hurlingham (Box 270)
    - Reason Versus Sentiment / Lillian Beynon Thomas, includes R. Oliphant reader report (Box 270)
    - The Reign of Misrule / Jesse F. Gelders (Box 270)
    - The Report of Byan Jay / Russ Meservey (Box 270)
    - Retreat / Clifford Dowdey, includes editorial note (Box 270)
    - Richard David Morton, Soldier of Chance / Mark Miller, from inventory (Box 270)
    - Richard Wagner's Baton / Frederick R. Burton (Box 271)
    - The St. Nicholas 'Gig' / Oscar Hatch Hawley (Box 271)
    - Santa Claws / Theodore Seixas Solomons (Box 271)
    - The Scarlet Dragon / Philip [L.] Scruggs (Box 271)
    - Seaman's Doom / H.S. Derrickson (Box 271)
    - Secret Service Stories / Andrew Craig (Box 271)
    - Seven Ages of Woman / Robert E. Dean, together with other witicisms/fillers by L.D. Kerns, Bill Levine (Box 271)
    - Shanghai Nights / Edgar Daniel Kramer (Box 271)
    - She Knew She Was Good / Henri Duvernois (Box 271)
    - Sheltered Daughters / Howard Fitzalan (Box 271)
    - The Silent Witness / Nicholas Silver [a.k.a. Frederick Faust] (Box 271)
    - Silver Street / Edward L. McKenna (Box 271)
    - The Sinking Swamp / William MacMillan (Box 271)
    - Sketchbook of drawings by H. Edwards, includes letter (Box 271)
    - The Slave of Sacramento / Horace Fish (Box 271)
    - The Smart Guy / Edward J. McKinney, includes printed rejection (Box 271)
    - Smouldering Fires / R.V. Young (Box 271)
    - A Son of Old Eli / Charles Kroth Moser, including editorial notes; 2 folders (Box 271)
    - The Songs of the Spheres / Frank Blighton, 2 copies (Box 271)
    - Sorrow in Sin / R.V. Young (Box 271)
    - Speed / Mary N.S. Whiteley (Box 271)
    - The Striking Fate / R.V. Young (Box 271)
    - Sugar Is Sweet / Gyneth Y. Johnson (Box 271)
    - Sunrise / H. Charles McDermott (Box 271)
    - The Swamp Outlaw; or Life in the Louisiana Lowlands / Edward Sylvester Ellis [a.k.a. Captain Emerson Rodman], with unsigned holograph reader report; 2 folders (Box 271)
    - The Taste of Life / Georges Surdez (Box 272)
    - Teeth of War / Lee Fredericks, includes Newsweek clipping (Box 272)
    - The Three Pellets / Adele de Leeuw (Box 272)
    - Thrills Without Frills / J.R. Henderson (Box 272)
    - To a May Fly at Dusk / Lydia Kingsway (Box 272)
    - To Hell With Horses / Lewis Ort (Box 272)
    - The Train Dispatcher / Marlbury L. Thompson (Box 272)
    - Tremble, My Love / Contessa Fairfax Colt a.k.a. H.C. Colt] (Box 272)
    - The Trials of Commander McTurk / C.J. Cutcliffe Hynes, preliminary sketch (Box 272)
    - Troubled Waters / William MacLeod Raine (Box 272)
    - The Truth About the Advertising Profession / Roy Kammerman (Box 272)
    - Twenty -- Twenty-four / John H. Compton, includes editorial note (Box 272)
    - Twenty-five Thousand Dollars / Jack Woodford, includes re-typed version incorporating some revisions (Box 272)
    - The Twisted Room / Vail Vernon, includes E.C. Richards reader report (Box 272)
    - Under False Colors / Harry J. Flinkman (Box 272)
    - W.W. Protects Posterity / Sheldon Wills, includes re-typed version (Box 272)
    - Wanted Angel / Ria A. Niccoli (Box 272)
    - What It Was / R.V. Young (Box 272)
    - When I Remember Marcia / Margaret Manners (Box 272)
    - When Last Seen... / Mortimer Braus (Box 272)
    - Whirlwind / R.V. Young (Box 272)
    - The White Dove / Perry E. Hackett (Box 272)
    - The White Draught / James Barr, from the pages of The Red Magazine, with card to editor of The Popular Magazine suggesting inclusion, and indicating the initiation of a copyright search (Box 272)
    - The White-Goat Sacrifice [alternate title: "The Spitting Swede"] / Charles M. Boone, includes editorial note (Box 272)
    - Who Made That Match? / Eleanor O'Malley Dillon (Box 272)
    - Who's Loony Now? / R.E. Dupuy (Box 272)
    - Wild-Fire [alternate titles "Atoms and the Man"; "The Atomic Gun"; "The Atomic Menace"; "The Brass Camera"; "The Red-Eyes"; "The Irresistibles"] / no author (Box 272)
    - Sowers of Strife) / L.H. Robbins (Box 272)
    - With the Rattle / R.V. Young (Box 272)
    - The Wolf Pack Chapter XXII Heart and Hand / Caroline Lockhart (Box 272)
    - The Wood Phantom [alternate title: "The Spectre of the Woods"] / Edward Sylvester Ellis [a.k.a. R.M. Hawthorne], ch. 1-25; 3 folders (Box 272)
    - The Wood Phantom (alternate title: "The Spectre of the Woods") / Edward Sylvester Ellis [a.k.a. R.M. Hawthorne], ch. 26-34 (Box 273)
    - Woodland Lore / Morton A. Howard, 7parts (Box 273)
    - Writhing Branches [alternate titles "Nero's Villa"; "The Man Eating Tree"] / J. Joseph-Renaud (Box 273)
    - Yankees Chivalrous [alternate titles "A Yankee Knight"; "Sam Dutton, Knight"; "The Chivalry of Sam Dutton"; "Yankee Gallants"; "Yankees Gallant"] / L.H. Robbins, partial manuscript of Chapter I, The Miracle (Box 273)
    - A Yellow Hero? / M. Henderson (Box 273)
    - The Yellow Mark of Courage / Philip Scruggs, includes editorial note (Box 273)
    - Untitled manuscript / Frank W. Chase, partial; includes letter, edited pp. 23-40, new last chapter (Box 273)
    - Untitled manuscript / Frederick Faust for Western Story Magazine (Box 273)
    - Untitled / Ruth Jones (Box 273)
    - Untitled / I. M. Marsal, includes printed rejection (Box 273)
    - Untitled manuscript / no author (Box 273)
    - Untitled manuscript / no author, p. 1 lacking (Box 273)
    - Fragments from 3 unidentified manuscripts, p. 30; pp. 17, 18, 20; pp. 26-44 (Box 273)
  - Motion Picture Department manuscripts
    - Contracts, 1914-1935; 3 folders (Box 273)
    - Inventory of "transactions of Carl Milligan around 1920" (Box 273)
    - Inventories of manuscripts, 1937; undated (Box 273)
    - The Black Company / W.B.M. Ferguson, originally appeared in The Popular Magazine; 5 copies in 2 folders (Box 274)
    - The Blucher of Wheat / George Bronson-Howard, published under name Howard Fitzallan (Box 274)
    - The Chase of the Christmas Gold Brick / Francis Lynde, published under name Edmund Dagobert in The Popular Magazine; 3 copies (Box 274)
    - The Detour / L.H. Robbins, originally appeared in The Popular Magazine (Box 274)
    - Devised and Bequeathed / Donn Byrne, 2 copies (Box 274)
    - Feet of Clay / W.B.M. Ferguson, published under name William Morton in The Popular Magazine; 2 copies (Box 274)
    - Flat Gold / James B. Hendryx, 2 copies (Box 274)
    - The Forty-Ninth Talesman / Holman Day, originally appeared in The Popular Magazine; 2 copies (Box 274)
    - The Gashing Fiddlers / Holman Day, originally appeared in The Popular Magazine; 2 copies (Box 274)
    - It's a Man's Country / Arthur Chapman, originally appeared in The Popular Magazine (Box 274)
    - The Keeper of the Keys / W. Beall Baldwin [a.k.a. Louis Joseph Vance], originally appeared in The Popular Magazine (Box 274)
    - Little Sister of the Stars / A.M. Chisholm (Box 274)
    - Mock Don Yuen Meditates / Lemuel L. Le Bra, published under name Lemuel L. De Bra (Box 274)
    - One Day's Work / Peter B. Kyne (Box 275)
    - The Psychomancers / Holman [F.] Day, originally appeared in The Popular Magazine; 3 copies (Box 275)
    - Robber's Roost / William McLeod Raine, published under name William MacLeod Raine in The Popular Magazine; 3 copies (Box 275)
    - The Springs of Youth / William H. Hamby, 2 copies (Box 275)
    - The Test / Louis Joseph Vance, originally appeared in The Popular Magazine (Box 275)
    - The Tolliver Tangle / Louis Joseph Vance, published under name George Parsons Bradford (Box 275)
    - The Treasure and the Secret Word / Thomas McMorrow, 3 copies (Box 275)
    - A Two-Spot in the Big Game / Holman Day, originally appeared in The Popular Magazine; 3 copies (Box 275)
    - The Unknown Quantity / Howard Fielding, originally appeared in The Popular Magazine (Box 275)
    - The Yield / Louis Joseph Vance, published under name J. Colville-Johnston; 2 copies (Box 275)
- Editorial files, miscellaneous
  - Atlas Publishing & Distributing Co. Ltd., 1950-1962; undated (Box 275)
  - Bindery estimates
    - American Book Bindery (Box 275)
    - Butler-Ward Company (Box 275)
    - Decorative Designers (Box 275)
    - Ives (Box 275)
    - North River (Box 275)
    - Wolf/Wolfe/Wolff (Box 275)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 275)
  - Bragin, Charles, 1943-1958; undated (Box 275)
  - Brown, Curtis - list of stories sold (Box 275)
  - Chelsea House
    - Book rights purchased, 1924-Mar. 1935 (Box 276)
    - Catalog of publications, See Promotional material: Catalogs.
    - Contracts with authors, 1921-1927; undated (Box 276)
    - Copyright transfers to authors (2), 1930 (Box 276)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, 1924-1935; 1951,; undated (Box 276)
    - Destruction of printing plates, alphabetical by author, 1934 (Box 276)
      Authors:
      Beale, Will
      Booth, Christopher
      Buck, Charles Neville Chisholm, A. M.
      Clark, Ellery H.
      Daniels, J. E.
      Faust, Frederick
      Fellom, James
      Ferguson, W. B. M.
      Gilbert, George
      Hamby, William H.
      Hankins, Arthur Preston
      Kauffman, Reginald W.
      Landon, Herman
      Livingston, Armstrong
      Lynde, Francis
      MacIsaac, Fred
      Perry, Clay
      Poate, Ernest M.
      Treynor, Albert N.
      Winter, William West
    - Inventories of books (Box 276)
    - Inventories of sheet stock, American Book Bindery, 1940-1942; undated (Box 276)
    - Popular copyright contracts
      - Miscellaneous, 1923-1938; 4 folders (Box 276)
      - A.L. Burt, 1921-1927; 1942; includes correspondence (Box 276)
      - Translations, 1928-1934 (Box 276)
    - Royalty statements, 1924-1927; 4 folders (Box 276)
  - Clippings, re: cessation of pulp publishing, 1949 (Box 276)
  - Contracts
    - Certificate of incorporation of PicPix, Inc. (Box 276)
    - Popular copyright contracts, See Chelsea House.
    - Miscellaneous, 1905-1919 (Box 276)
    - Standard form for the sale of magazine rights (Box 276)
  - Copyright renewals, by series
    - Memo, 1937? (Box 276)
    - Border #138-#206, [1937-1939] (Box 277)
    - Eagle and New Eagle #676, #730, [1937-1938] (Box 277)
    - Great Western #48-#156, [1937-1939] (Box 277)
    - Magnet and New Magnet #726-#1351, [1937-1942] (Box 277)
    - Merriwell #179-#245, [1937-1942] (Box 277)
  - Critiques
    - Assigned
      - Arrow Library (Box 277)
      - Bertha Clay Library (Box 277)
      - Boys of Liberty Library (Box 277)
      - Dr. Jack Series (Box 277)
      - Harkaway Library (Box 277)
      - Magnet Library (Box 277)
    - Unassigned, by author
      - Cobb, Benjamin F. (Box 277)
      - Cobb, Sylvanus (Box 277)
      - De Morgan, John (Box 277)
      - Fleming, May Agnes (Box 277)
      - Hardenbrook, William Ten Eyck (Box 277)
      - Hawks, Wells (Box 277)
      - Hornung, Ernest William (Box 277)
      - Lee, Margaret (Box 277)
      - McCardell, Roy (Box 277)
      - Raymond, Evelyn (Box 277)
      - Sheldon, Georgie (Box 277)
    - Unassigned, by title, 2 folders (Box 277)
  - [Alexandre] Dumas translations
    - Correspondence of and memoranda relating to Henry Llewellyn Williams, 1902-1903; undated (Box 277)
    - Critique, The Lovely Lady Hamilton (Box 277)
    - Hints to artist re Dumas' The Tower of Nesle (Box 277)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 277)
  - Financial
    - Art vouchers, alphabetical by originator, A-Q, 7 folders (Box 277)
    - Art vouchers, alphabetical by originator, S-Z (Box 278)
    - Manuscript vouchers, alphabetical by author (Box 278)
    - Calculations and notes, 1904; 1937,; undated (Box 278)
  - Inventory of series
    Disbound notebooks are listed first, followed by other material.
    - Adventure Library, 1926-1931; notebook, disbound (Box 278)
    - Alger Series, 1926-1933; notebook, disbound (Box 278)
    - Great Western Library, 1927-1932; notebook, disbound (Box 278)
    - Love Story Library, 1926-1932; notebook, disbound (Box 278)
    - Merriwell/Standish, 1921-1933; notebook, disbound (Box 278)
    - New Bertha Clay Library, 1926-1932; notebook, disbound (Box 278)
    - New Eagle Series, 1926-1932; notebook, disbound (Box 278)
    - New Magnet Library, 1926-1933; notebook, disbound (Box 278)
    - Round the World Library, 1926-1931; notebook, disbound (Box 278)
    - [Burt L.] Standish Library, See Merriwell/Standish.
    - Western Story Library, 1927-1930; notebook, disbound (Box 278)
    - [Bertha] Clay Library, 1904; no.s 241-249 (Box 278)
    - Favorite Library, undated; no.s 251-325 (Box 278)
    - Harkaway Library, circa 1904 (Box 278)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 278)
  - Lists of authors' stories from Street & Smith publications, individual authors, 2 folders (Box 278)
    Authors included:
    Adams, Cleve F.
    Alger, Horatio
    Apple, A. E.
    Archibald, Joe
    Bond, Lee
    Bradbury, Ray
    Breslauer, Bernard
    Buck, Charles Neville
    Cartmill, Cleve
    Chapel, Charles E.
    Chapin, Cyrus
    Chester, George Randolph
    Cook, William Wallace
    Dent, Lester
    Dingle, A. E.
    Dunning, Hal
    England, George Allan
    Ervin, Patrick - see Howard, Robert Ervin
    Fearn, John Russell
    Ferguson [W. B. M.?]
    Ferrill, Benjamin F.
    Gelzer, Jay (Mrs.) [a.k.a. John Paul Mitchell]
    Gibson, Walter B.
    Gregory, Jackson
    Gross, Michael
    Heinlein, Robert A.
    Holmes, Mary J.
    Howard, Robert Ervin
    Irvine, Houston
    Jenkins, Will F.
    Lewis, Alfred Henry
    Liebe, Hapsburg
    Lincoln, Joseph C.
    Lockhart, Caroline
    Mann, Arthur
    McClary, Thomas Calvert [a.k.a. Calvin Peregoy]
    McNutt, William Slavens
    Mitchell, John Paul - see Gelzer, Jay (Mrs.)
    Page, Norvell
    Pape, Lee
    Penrose, Bernard Lee
    Peregoy, Calvin - see McClary, Thomas Calvert
    Phillips, Roland Ashford
    Powers, Paul S. (a.k.a. Ward M. Stevens)
    Randall, William Herbert
    Rathborne, St. George
    Ridge, Lola
    Rohmer, Sax
    Rothenberger, Paul
    Saltus, Edgar
    Sheridan, Phil R.
    Smith, Edward H.
    Stebbins, Francis L.
    Stevens, Ward M. - see Powers, Paul S.
    Stillman, Donald
    Terhune, Albert Payson
    Tinsley, Theodore
    Tompkins, Walker
    Tuttle, W. C.
    Ward, John Lawrence
    Ward, J. R.
    Wells, H. G.
    Whiteley, Mary N. S.
    Wire, H. C.
    Witwer, H. C.
  - Lists of authors' stories from Street & Smith publications, multiple authors (Box 278)
  - Lists of newspapers for review copies, 1901; undated; 2 folders (Box 278)
  - Literary Features Ltd., 1962 (Box 278)
  - Luzzato, Jack, 1944-1949; undated; regarding word puzzles) with "What's in a Brand?" puzzles (Box 278)
  - Manuscript transferrals
    - By periodical title, A-Z on cards, 3 folders (Box 278)
    - By date, 1930-1937; undated (Box 278)
  - Memoranda
    - Editorial Department organization, Sept. 27, 1937 (Box 278)
    - Internal inquiries and reports about stock, 1903-1904; undated (Box 278)
    - Literary agents who submit to Street and Smith, Jan. 20, 1939 (Box 278)
    - Manuscripts titles, miscellaneous (i.e. not assigned to a particular periodical), 1940; undated (Box 278)
    - Revised series lists sent to various departments, 1903-1905; cover notes only, no lists attached (Box 278)
    - Miscellaneous, 1927; 1934,; 1938-1939,; 1944 (Box 278)
  - [F. Tennyson] Neely, Publisher/Roth, H. William
    - Correspondence, 1899 (Box 279)
  - Notebooks
    - Compilation of information on competitors and distributors, as well as data on Street & Smith periodicals, 1939-1940; disbound (Box 279)
    - Personnel and publications records, undated (Box 279)
  - Orders
    - Ainslee's/Select Fiction, 1903-1904; undated; 5 folders (Box 279)
    - American News Co., 1903-1905; 1932 (Box 279)
    - Federal Book Company, 1904-1905; undated; 3 folders (Box 279)
    - Kaufman Advertising Agency, 1903 (Box 279)
    - Miscellaneous, 1903-1904 (Box 279)
    - Daily report, Stock and Returned Goods Department, June 18, 1900 (Box 279)
  - Photographs
    - Indexed, 21 items (Box 279)
      1. 79 Seventh Ave., NY - exterior of building
      2. Reception room at 15th St., 79 Seventh Ave.
      3. Corridor outside general offices (1906)
      4. General office, from the SE (1906)
      5. Clarence Vernon's office (1906)
      6. Ormond G. Smith's office, from the NW
      7. Private office, for out-of-town friends (1906)
      8. Accounting Department, cashier's office (1906)
      9. Composing room
      10. Linotype room, from the SE
      11. Pressroom, from the SE
      12. Pressroom, from the SW (1906)
      13. Feeding press, showing flyboy and pressman (1906)
      14. Flatbed press
      15. Foundry (1906)
      16. Paper stock room (1906)
      17. Bindery, showing folding machines (1910)
      18. Bindery
      19. Book Department (1906)
      20. Book Department
      21. Freight elevator, 15th Street
    - Indexed, in binder, same as above; 21 items (Box 280)
    - Street & Smith interior offices and production spaces, same as above, but larger; includes some photocopies (Oversize 12)
    - Unidentified, 5 items (Box 279)
  - Plate stock inventories
    - Books by classification, undated (Box 279)
    - Books by Edgar Saltus, undated (Box 279)
    - Books [for] which Dillingham has the right to use our plates, 1904 (Box 279)
    - Duplicate plates, undated (Box 279)
    - List of unpublished books arranged alphabetically by titles, undated (Box 279)
    - Lists arranged by series titles, 1904; undated; 2 folders (Box 279)
    - Miscellaneous undated (Box 279)
  - Promotional material
    - Catalogs
      - Street & Smith's Complete Catalogue and Order List of Popular Ten Cent Books, 1899 (Box 279)
      - Cloth Book Department Descriptive List of Publications, 1903 (Box 279)
      - News Trade Bulletin, 1930 (Box 279)
      - Publications of Chelsea House, 1933 (Box 279)
      - Subscription Price List of Magazines, 1940? (Box 279)
      - Street & Smith's Arrow Library, Undated (Box 279)
    - Other
      - Advertising copy for Campaigning with Tippecanoe / John H. Whitson (Box 279)
      - The Bookseller complimentary directory of representatives for exhibit, July 1903 (Box 279)
      - The Greatest Publishing House in the World, circa 1905; booklet commemorating the 50th anniversary of Street & Smith, edited for possible later use (Box 279)
      - Submission form for The Publisher's Weekly (Box 279)
  - Purchases
    - American Publishers Corporation
      - List of books sold us carrying royalties (Box 279)
    - [Robert] Bonner's Sons
      - Catalogue of publications, printed material, with annotations (Box 279)
      - Inventory of "Illustrations received from Bonne'rs Sons" (Box 279)
      - Inventory of plates purchased (Box 279)
      - Inventories of plates purchased, with additional pages indicating royalty agreements (Box 279)
      - Inventories of titles in The Ledger Library and The Popular Series (Box 281)
      - Inventory of "used or discontinued Bonner books" (Box 281)
    - [N.L.] Munro
      - Golden Hours
        - Assignments
          - Might and Main Library, undated (Box 281)
          - New Ten-Cent Library, undated (Box 281)
          - Reserved for book publication, Nov. 16, 1906 (Box 281)
          - Various, Nov. 16, 1906; undated (Box 281)
        - Inventory of titles arranged by author (Box 281)
        - Inventories of titles selected for purchase, 1902-1908; undated; 3 folders (Box 281)
        - Inventories of titles not purchased or unavailable, 1905; undated (Box 281)
      - Old Cap. Collier Library
        - Assignments
          - Boys of America, undated (Box 281)
          - Magnet Library, 1903; undated (Box 281)
          - New Secret Service Series, 1903; undated (Box 281)
          - Nick Carter Weekly, 1903-1904 (Box 281)
          - Old Broadbrim Weekly, 1904; undated (Box 281)
          - The Jesse James Stories, undated (Box 281)
          - Various, 1904; undated (Box 281)
        - Inventories of numbers sold, 1902-1907; undated (Box 281)
        - Inventories of numbers wanted, reserved, used, not used, in stock, etc. (Box 281)
        - Inventories of titles, printed material (Box 281)
        - Inventories of titles sold (481) (Box 281)
        - Inventories of titles sold, 1st-5th selections (Box 281)
        - Inventory of "23 selected serials from Golden Hours in place of 69 Old Cap Collier stories" (Box 281)
        - Notes, miscellaneous (Box 281)
  - Queries, by date of reply, 1937-1969; 6 folders (Box 281)
    See also Bragin, Charles.